// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
  answer: "Bytecode is executed by JVM",
  options: [
    "Bytecode is executed by JVM",
    "The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
    "Use of exception handling",
    "Dynamic binding between objects"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which of the following is not a Java features??",
  answer: "Use of pointers",
  options: [
    "Dynamic",
    "Architecture Neutral",
    "Use of pointers",
    "Object-oriented"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: " The \u0021 article referred to as a",
  answer: "Unicode escape sequence",
  options: [
    "Unicode escape sequence",
    "Octal escape",
    "Hexadecimal",
    "Line feed"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "  _____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.",
  answer: "JDB",
  options: [
    "JVM",
    "JVD",
    "JDB",
    "JDK"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: " Which of the following is a valid declaration of a char?",
  answer: " char ch = 'tea';",
  options: [
    "char ch = 'tea';",
    "char ca = 'tea';",
    "char cr = \u0223;",
    "char cc = '\itea';"
  ]
},
{
numb: 6,
  question: " What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?",
  answer: "Infinity",
  options: [
    "0",
    "Not a Number",
    "Infinity",
    "Run time exception"
  ]
},
{
numb: 7,
  question: " Which of the following tool is used to generate API documentation in HTML format from doc comments in source code",
  answer: " Javadoc tool",
  options: [
    "javap tool",
    "javaw command",
    "Javadoc tool",
    "javah command"
  ]
},
{
numb: 8,
  question: "  Which of the following for loop declaration is not valid?",
  answer: " for ( int i = 99; i>=0; i / 9)",
  options: [
    "for ( int i = 99; i >= 0; i / 9 )",
    "for ( int i = 7; i <= 77; i += 7 )",
    "for ( int i = 20; i >= 2; - -i )",
    "for ( int i = 2; i <= 20; i = 2* i )"
  ]
},
{
numb: 9,
  question: " What do you mean by nameless objects?",
  answer: " An object that has no reference.",
  options: [
    "An object created by using the new keyword.",
    "An object of a superclass created in the subclass",
    " An object that has no reference",
    "An object without having any name but having a reference"
  ]
},
{
numb: 10,
  question: "An interface with no fields or methods is known as a ______.",
  answer: "Marker Interface",
  options: [
    "Runnable Interface",
    "Marker Interface",
    "Abstract Interface",
    "CharSequence Interface"
  ]
},


];